How'd he get to you? Who?
That federal agent, Paul Davies.
He said that it was absolutely
imperative that I plead guilty.
He said that the investigation
he was spearheading
would clear me
and he promised me
that I wouldn't
spend a day in prison.
What's the matter with you?
He can't promise
that. Nobody can.
The system isn't
made to work that way.
Why didn't you consult
with me before you agreed?
He said not to
discuss it with anyone.
He said it was a matter
of national security.
Well, maybe that's what he said,
but that's not why you complied.
He promised you an
exclusive, didn't he?
He told you you
could break the story
as soon as his
investigation was over.
You weren't thinking
about national security.
You were thinking
about a Pulitzer Prize.
You lied, and if this
investigation comes up dry
or loses its funding
or just plain folds,
you just made the
biggest mistake of your life.
Yeah, Tyler. Did you find him?
Oh, yeah. Paul Davies?
Yep, and he wants
to talk to you too.
Good.
Paul Davies,
section chief, special projects.
Now, what's this all about?
You don't know anything
about a secret investigation?
No, and furthermore,
no one in this office
is conducting any
investigation that involves you.
The IDs these guys were flashing
didn't come out of a cereal box.
Did anybody quit
your staff recently?
No one fitting the description
of the men you saw.
Damn. Impersonating
a federal agent's
a serious offense, Mr. Matlock,
and I assure you we will
look into this immediately.
I've got a client
who just confessed to
murder in open court.
Unless I find who
talked her into that,
she could go to prison
for the rest of her life.
And you think the person
that killed this Karen Wyler
is behind all this?
Yes, got to be,
and I think it's one of the men
my office has
been investigating.
Lambert Crawford, for
one. Lambert Crawford?
Senator Lambert Crawford? Yes.
That's who Karen
Wyler was working for
at the time she was murdered.
She believed that
he, Michael Fitzmorris,
Robert Irwin... Robert Irwin?
The attorney. And that whiz kid
who ran the senator's
reelection campaign, Jed Palmer.
She told my client, who
works for the newspaper,
that they were up to something
involving a lot of money
and a lot of secrecy.
Now, doesn't it stand to reason
that's why she was murdered?
What kind of proof did she have?
She didn't.
And neither do I.
He told her she'd be helping
her country, Your Honor.
She was tricked into
making that confession.
Your Honor, I was approached
and fooled by these same men.
My client is innocent.
I wanna clear her of these
charges as soon as possible,
but I need the time to find
these phony federal agents.
Your Honor, I'd
like a continuance.
Denied. Next suggestion.
Then I'll move for a mistrial.
I'll deny that too.
How'd it go?
He shouldn't be
removed from the bench.
He should be removed
from the planet.
That well, huh? Cheer up.
Remember the car that
followed Michelle and Jed Palmer
to his apartment,
the one that belonged
to those alleged G-men? Yeah.
I traced the license
plate and found out
who it's registered to. Who?
The Leyland Group.
Who's the Leyland Group?
It's some kind of
giant holding company,
but the most interesting
thing here is the legal counsel
that they've retained
here in Washington.
Who?
Robert Irwin.
Oh.
How about getting
together with Jed Palmer?
See what he knows about this
Leyland Group and Robert Irwin.
Is there a problem?
No. No problem.
Coming.
Hello.
Hi.
Welcome back.
Come on in.
I've got some espresso.
It'll be ready in just a minute.
Oh, no. None for me, thank you.
No. It's no problem.
I need to talk to you.
I've got nothing
against talking.
It comes in, uh, pretty
handy sometimes.
You never know
where it might lead.
I wasn't exactly
forthcoming with you last time
about who I am.
You're not Michelle Thomas?
I am, but I'm also an attorney.
I work with Ben Matlock.
Defending Melinda Stuart?
That's right.
You're very good.
Thanks.
You, uh... You set me up.
Set you up? Yeah.
You had me completely fooled.
I didn't lie to you.
No, but you kept
certain things from me.
When I look at you, I see
a bright, interesting woman.
Someone I can relate
to. Someone I can...
be comfortable with.
A woman I can spend
special time with.
You set me up.
What did you want from me?
Just someone to
answer your questions?
I'm really sorry.
I apologize.
But I need to ask
you a couple more.
Why not?
Ever hear of the Leyland Group?
Sure. It's some
big conglomerate.
Principal interests are oil.
Headquarters in
Houston, I think.
Ask Michael Fitzmorris.
He used to work for them.
What's Robert Irwin's
connection to them?
I'm afraid you'd
have to ask him that.
What about his
connection to Karen Wyler?
He ever have an affair with her?
Again, you'd have to ask him.
What about Crawford?
You'd have to ask him too.
What about you?
Of what possible
relevance is any of this?
Whoever actually killed
her was very familiar
with the burglar alarm
system in her apartment,
and I imagine very
familiar with her.
Which rules me out.
I was at the Brazilian
embassy that whole evening
with 150 other people.
She told Melinda
that your relationship
with Senator Crawford went
beyond being a media consultant.
What's that supposed to mean?
I was hoping you'd tell me.
I wish I could, but I can't.
Too bad you can't ask Karen.
Yeah. It's too bad.
Well, thanks for the talk.
Anytime, Michelle.
And, uh, listen.
Next time you have a
question to ask me, just ask.
Don't set me up.
Well, if it's information you
were looking for, Mr. Matlock,
you have definitely
come to the right place.
You know, many people,
my husband included,
regard me as nothing but
a flighty, garrulous old fool.
Well, not only do I
have eyes in my head,
I have a brain as well.
Oh, I could tell that
the instant I met you.
In fact, I... I said to
Michelle, I... I said,
"Michelle, there
is a smart woman."
You know what she said?
What? "I know it."
Oh, she is such
a wonderful girl.
Oh, isn't she?
You are a very, very
lucky man. I know. I know.
Now, what do you know about
your husband's connection
with the Leyland Group?
More than I'm supposed
to, I can tell you that.
You know, I knew
something was up
when Robert started to
lock the door of his study
whenever they'd
call him at home.
Well, I mean, that only served
to pique my desire
to learn more.
Oh. So... did you?
Mm. Are you sure that you
won't have one of these?
They are quite delicious.
Oh, no, thank you, Miss Irwin.
Oh, please, please.
Clarissa.
You know, whenever
anyone calls me Mrs. Irwin,
I tend to look over my shoulder
expecting to see
Robert's mother.
Which is a little disconcerting,
as she died seven years ago.
Did you, uh...?
Did you find out?
About what?
The Leyland Group.
Oh, the Leyland Group.
Excuse me. Mr. Matlock,
you have a phone
call from a Mr. Davies.
Which one?
All I know is he says
it's an emergency.
Oh, please go ahead
and take it. I'm in no hurry.
Uno más. Ahem.
This is Ben Matlock.
Hello?
Hey, Clarissa!
I'm telling you there's
a conspiracy afoot,
and my client is innocent.
Is this the same client who
confessed in open court?
She was tricked into
that by the same people
who kidnapped Clarissa Irwin.
Lieutenant, what
is this all about?
Sorry to bother you,
but Mr. Matlock here
claims your wife
has been kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
Do you have any idea
where she is right now?
I know precisely
where she is right now.
She's down in Texas at a
spa called, uh, the Springs.
Call the place and get
Mrs. Irwin on the line.
I know I had lunch
with her, at least tried to.
I really don't
have time for this.
Call the maitre d' at Rex's.
- We did.
He says while you
were on the phone,
Mrs. Irwin got up and
left with two gentlemen.
Those gentlemen are
impersonating federal agents.
Lieutenant, line one.
Mrs. Irwin? Hello.
This is James Norris from
the Washington, D.C. police.
Fine, thank you.
More to the point, how
are you, Mrs. Irwin?
Oh. Sorry, uh, Clarissa.
Uh.
Clarissa?
Ben Matlock. What in
the world's going on?
I do apologize for getting
up and leaving like that,
but I'd entirely forgotten
that I booked myself in
for a stay down here.
And the spa is just
dreadful about no-shows.
I'm sorry, Ben. I have to go.
Whatever it is
you're trying to pull,
I advise you
not to try it again.
Thank you for coming down
and helping us clear this up.
My apologies.
Okay.
- The Springs?
- Yeah.
Some kind of spa in Texas.
Well, what am I supposed
to do when I find her?
Talk to her.
We've got to find out what
her husband's connection is
with the Leyland Group.
Now, she was kidnapped?
I thought so. Well, if she was,
what if the people who did it
don't want her to talk to me?
Find a way. BOTH: You always do.
Their identification
looked real.
It looked real.
I honestly believed that
they were federal agents.
So I did what they asked me to.
I confessed.
Melinda, did you
shoot Karen Wyler?
No.
That's all, thank you.
Just tell me this, Miss Stuart.
Were you lying the other
day, or were you lying just now,
or were you lying both times
and have yet
another tale to tell us?
Um... Approach the
bench, Your Honor?
Your Honor, I submit
that you're impugning
the credibility of my client
with your every word,
gesture, and expression.
And if you continue,
I'll have no choice
but to move to have Your
Honor disqualified for prejudice.
Lack of impartiality is probably
the most serious charge
that can be leveled against
someone in my position.
Are you certain that your
observations are not colored
by your own
partiality, Mr. Matlock?
Your Honor, I'm
supposed to be partial.
I'm the defense.
Mr. Hobbs, are you aware
of any demonstrations
of prejudice on my part?
No, Your Honor. No.
Then I suggest not only that
you reconsider your options,
Mr. Matlock,
but that you bear
this in mind as well:
I have never been
removed for cause,
but I have cited many,
many lawyers for contempt.
Do I make myself clear?
Abundantly.
Should I repeat the
question, Miss Stuart?
I lied before, I admit that,
but I did not kill Karen Wyler.
Let me point out that
it doesn't excuse her
because she was lying before...
- Mr. Matlock,
I asked Miss
Stuart the question.
Your Honor, I am this
woman's defense attorney.
I have the right to speak.
When she confessed,
she was not under oath.
She is under oath now.
Her statement that she
did not kill Karen Wyler
is for the record!
Mr. Matlock, sit down!
Believe me, Mr. Davenport,
if discretion and results
are what you want,
the Springs is unsurpassed.
Good, because that's
exactly what I'd heard.
And we are particularly
adept at meeting the needs
of people who
are... Well-heeled?
Well, since we seem to
understand each other,
what exactly is
your wife's problem?
She is, uh... fat.
Well, a weight problem
is no problem for us.
Look, why don't I
take you on a little tour
and I'll show you how we deal
with our food dependencies.
As soon as I answer this call.
Please, why don't
you have a seat outside
and I'll be right with you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this is the manager.
No, we have not
received those orders yet,
and I would like for you
to check on that for me.
Mr. Davenport?
Hey!
I don't know. I just...
I just locked myself out.
Tyler...
You've gotta get back in
there and get Clarissa out.
Whoever we're dealing with
might decide to make
her stay permanent.
Do you understand?
Okay, okay.
I'll be in touch.
Clarissa Irwin is
at that spa in Texas
under heavy sedation.
The Springs is owned
by the Leyland Group.
I'm gonna listen to the
tapes that Melinda made
of her interviews with Karen
to see if there's
anything on them
that might tell us something
Melinda may have overlooked.
As usual, you're two
steps ahead of me.
Where are you going?
Once you get a fire started,
you've gotta stir the pot.
There's always work to be done.
That's why I love this job.
This country never stands still.
It's always moving.
Growing.
Changing.
I've helped clean
up after World War II.
I've done my damndest
to prevent World War III.
I've come through
missile crises, oil crises,
overseen aid to our schools,
aid to our farmers.
Never the same thing twice.
I like to think that means
that we must've been
doing something right.
Yeah.
I, uh, I... I admire
people in public office.
I really do.
Uh, didn't you become chairman
of the Senate committee
that polices the activities
of big oil companies
about the time
of the oil crisis?
That's right. I have
reason to believe
that the Leyland Group...
Y-You're familiar with the
Leyland Group, are you?
Yes, of course.
It's a conglomerate
which owns several
oil companies.
I have reason to believe
that the Leyland Group
is somehow involved
in Karen Wyler's murder.
Why would they want
to murder my secretary?
I don't know. I don't know,
but I do know that
Michael Fitzmorris,
your legislative assistant,
used to work for them.
Mike, step in here, please.
It could be that it's
just a coincidence,
or it could be that he's
some sort of watchdog
who's supposed to make sure
that a certain elected
official holds up his end
of whatever deal was struck
with this Leyland Group.
I don't think I like what
you're implying, Mr. Matlock.
What's going on?
I was just sounding out a couple
of ideas on the senator here,
asking him if, uh, he
thinks maybe a person
who thought he
was facing retirement
might've gotten a little greedy
and allowed himself
to be bought off.
After all, 40 years is a long
time to remain idealistic,
isn't it, senator?
What the hell are
you suggesting?
Oh, nothing. Nothing,
just shooting off my mouth.
I guess it comes from
sitting in a courtroom all day.
Oh, uh, uh, I spoke
with that security guard
about, uh, your being up here
working with the senator
at the time of the murder.
He said that he
saw you around 8,
and the murder occurred
in Karen's apartment
around 9.
Mrs. Irwin?
Mrs. Irwin, wake up.
You're being released.
You can change
in the truck. Truck?
Oh, yeah, and we're
all out of wheelchairs,
so you... You can ride in this.
There you go.
Truck?
Wait a minute. Wa...
Hey, wait a minute.
Let me give you
a hand there, pal.
Let's go.
Gee, what you got
in here? A dead cow?
That's it. I'll be
insulted no more.
Wait a minute! Hey!
What? What?
Somebody just drove
out of here with Mrs. Irwin.
So when Congressman
Levin didn't get re-elected,
he called Lambert's office
and got him to hire me.
Did you sleep with the senator?
Maybe I did, maybe I didn't.
Karen, I need details.
Telling you all this
is making me feel...
- Maybe this is a mistake.
- No, it's not.
Please, keep going.
What about Jed Palmer?
You get anything?
Anything usable?
Not so far, but maybe.
He can make you feel
like somebody special.
He said I was a bright,
interesting woman.
Somebody he could relate to.
Somebody he could
be comfortable with.
spend special time with.
Ha-ha. Well, I
guess it was special.
He got what he wanted.
I, uh, I slept with
him for a while,
then it was over,
and on the off chance
that there are still women
in this town he
hasn't slept with,
somebody ought to warn them.
He's a user and he's got
more lines than Shakespeare.
I don't believe it.
He makes me feel like a louse
for not being totally
honest with him,
and then he turns right around
and looks me straight in the eye
and gives me the same line.
Boy, he's in for it.
Wait a minute. You
can't go over there.
He might be the
one who killed Karen.
Then he's really in for it.
I think we can
freeze-frame right here
on the kid's eyes.
Super the client's name here
and have a voiceover say,
"Let's start tomorrow today.
Vote for Hal Rice."
That kind of thing.
Yeah?
I need to see you, Mr. Palmer.
Take five. Okay.
I heard what Karen
Wyler said about you.
I listened to a tape of an
interview she did with Melinda.
Guess what.
She said we had an affair.
You could say that, yeah.
I also checked with
the Brazilian embassy.
Guess what. Now, wait a minute.
I was there. You
arrived around 10.
Karen was murdered around 9.
Are you saying I'm a suspect?
You, Senator Crawford,
Michael Fitzmorris,
and Robert Irwin.
Michelle, I didn't kill her.
Just like you didn't
sleep with her?
All right, I lied. I was
trying to be discreet.
In my profession,
it's called perjury.
I just didn't want to say
something that might
jeopardize our... Our
budding relationship.
Budding relationship? Mmm-hm.
You say I'm a bright,
interesting woman.
Someone you can relate to.
Someone you can
be comfortable with.
That's the same line
you used on Karen.
All you were trying to do
was get me where you got her.
Truth and lies are
the same with you,
something you
just edit in or out.
You either wave it
around like a flag,
or you shove it in a drawer,
whichever happens to suit your
professional or sexual needs.
One woman is dead
and another faces
life imprisonment,
and all you're worried about
is our budding relationship?
Well, don't, 'cause
there ain't one.
Oh.
I feel like I've been
asleep for days.
You have been.
There's a thermos
of coffee on the floor.
Oh, you dear thing.
What foresight.
Any idea why your husband
would do this to you?
I know precisely
why he did this to me.
It was because of what
I was about to tell Ben.
What?
Sorrel Flats.
Who is Sorrel Flats?
I thought it was
a who at first too.
To be honest, I thought it
was one of Robert's mistresses,
something he was hiding
from me out of etiquette.
But finally I realized
he was hiding it from me
because he really
didn't want me to know.
But, of course, I made it
my business to find out.
He must've known I would.
Mrs. Irwin, what
is Sorrel Flats?
Oh, please, please.
Call me Clarissa.
Whenever anybody
calls me Mrs. Irwin,
I feel so terribly
uncomfortable.
Clarissa, what is Sorrel Flats?
A tank farm.
A tank farm?
Where they store oil.
Only there isn't any
oil at Sorrel Flats.
There isn't?
No, my husband and his friends
have been selling the
government oil that doesn't exist.
You sure?
Are we in the middle of nowhere?
Not anymore.
We're heading for home.
Hello, Michelle.
Now, before you get
excited, this is not an apology.
Then what is it,
another come-on?
Crawford, Fitzmorris,
Irwin, and I,
we were all taking payoffs
from the Leyland Group.
Actually, mine was
more of an annuity,
money they promised
me when I agreed
to run Crawford's
re-election campaign.
What was it for the others?
I don't know. They...
They pulled me over
to Crawford's office
every couple of months.
Fitzmorris would pass out the
cash he got down in Houston,
and we'd all go our separate
ways, no questions asked.
Who was calling the shots?
Irwin.
The night of the murder too?
In fact, he called
me that night.
He said that, uh,
Karen had stolen a ledger
from Crawford's desk.
There was nothing
incriminating in it,
but it proved that she was
the one leaking information
to Melinda at the Trib.
He said the others
were at Crawford's office
discussing the situation.
He asked me if I had any ideas.
I said no, and finally hung up.
That still doesn't explain why
you were late to that reception.
I was in bed with
a married woman.
How do I know this is the truth?
It sure as hell isn't a come-on.
No. Absolutely not.
No way. He's not
signing anything.
Not till we get the release.
That's what we agreed on
and that's the way
it's going to stand.
You can tell him I'm sorry.
Are you busy, Mr. Irwin?
Yes. As a matter of fact, I am.
Uh, too busy to say
hello to your wife?
That's right, Robert, darling.
I escaped from that hellhole
that you packed me off to.
If you're responsible
for this, you're through.
Any number of doctors, uh,
will testify that my
wife's mental health
is precarious at best.
He knows about Sorrel Flats.
You know, those big,
waterlogged oil tanks
that belong to all those
rich friends of yours?
Now see what you've done.
She's totally mad.
You're drowning,
and if you think I'm
going to keep lying
about where you were when that
pathetic creature was murdered,
then you're the one who's mad.
Clarissa... He was not home
having dinner
with me that night.
In fact, I'll be damned
if I know where he was.
Uh...
I, uh, I know about
the Leyland Group.
I know about the
fraudulent oil sales.
I know about your meeting
in the senator's office
after Karen stole that ledger.
Is there anything else
I should know about?
Get out.
It's Robert.
Um... It's all coming unraveled.
Yeah.
It's gonna be every
man for himself.
So it was Robert
Irwin that killed her?
Well, I'm not
certain it was him.
What are we looking for?
I don't know.
Maybe the police
overlooked something.
They had Melinda. Maybe
they missed something.
Yeah, but the only fingerprints
they found belonged to her.
Yeah.
Whoever did it did a pretty
good job of cleaning it up.
Well, we know he set the
burglar alarm before he ran.
And he had to have
deactivated it before he entered.
He must've wiped off the panel.
There weren't any prints
found at all, not even hers.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did a pretty
good job of cleaning it up.
Hm.
I wonder if Karen had big hands.
I don't know. Huh.
Looks like a medium or a large.
You think... Well, it might be.
Somebody used these to
clean up after the murder
and then put 'em back in the
bucket where he found 'em.
Now, that is a good theory.
Why don't we take
'em down to the lab
and have a technician turn
them wrong side out real careful?
You want...? Yeah.
Let's take the whole thing.
You got me.
My name is Lambert Crawford.
I'm a United States senator.
I reside in San Antonio, Texas,
and I also have a residence
in the District of Columbia.
Thank you, senator.
For the past ten years,
you've been chairman of a
Senate committee that monitors,
among other things,
federal oil purchases.
Is that correct? Yes, it is.
And the oil the government
purchases from an oil company
called the Leyland Group
is stored at a place
called Sorrel Flats.
Is that correct? I
don't recall offhand.
I'd have to check my records.
And I have to ask of
what possible relevance
is any of this?
I'm establishing
foundation, Your Honor.
The defense contends
that Karen Wyler
was killed because
she was convinced
that you and three other men
were part of a conspiracy.
Are you aware of that, senator?
I've heard that rumor, yes.
Now, isn't it true that
this Leyland Group
made substantial contributions
to your last campaign?
Again, I don't recall offhand,
but I'm sure if they did,
they were legitimate.
Isn't it true they did that
because they were
extremely eager
that you maintain your post
as chairman of that
Senate committee?
All of my political
supportees were interested
in my keeping my Senate posts.
Isn't it true that
this Leyland Group
has sold millions of dollars
of nonexistent oil
to the government?
Not to my knowledge, no.
And isn't it true you
would warn them
whenever government officials
were going to make spot checks
of their storage tanks
so they could move
the existing oil around,
making 3000 barrels
look like 300,000?
I have no knowledge
of anything like that.
And isn't it true that you
and three other men
accepted payoffs for your part
in this very
lucrative conspiracy?
And isn't it true that Karen
Wyler was on the verge
of finding out about it?
And isn't it true that's
why she was killed?
Objection. No foundation.
No relevancy. Speculation.
Sustained.
Mr. Matlock, you
are out of order.
You aren't establishing
foundation here.
You're using this witness
as a excuse to speculate,
and I won't have it.
Either you provide this court
with proof of
what you're saying,
or you move on to a
legitimate line of questioning.
Yes, sir.
We're checking into
your Swiss bank account.
That's not a question.
Matlock, I instruct you to
move on with your questions.
Yes, sir.
Was Karen Wyler your mistress?
She was my secretary.
Now, careful, senator.
Remember those department
store charge cards you gave her?
The bills would come
into the office each month.
You paid out-of-office expenses.
I don't know
anything about this.
She must've done
it behind my back.
How often did you
go to her apartment?
Once a week? Twice a week?
That's not true. Did
you tell her it was over?
Did you cut it off? Is that
why she went to Melinda Stuart
with what she knew
of the conspiracy?
Maybe to get back at you? No.
Is that why you decided
it'd be best for all concerned
if she were dead?
No, that's not true.
I swear it.
I cared about Karen.
I could never kill her.
Never.
That's it for this line of
questioning, Mr. Matlock.
You and your client may
revel in gossip and scandal,
but I assure you,
this court does not.
We're going to take a recess
for lunch now, counselor,
and when we return at 2:00 p.m.,
you will begin to elicit
relevant testimony
and only relevant testimony.
Is that clear?
You had to do it.
I know it.
I sure wish he hadn't
gotten involved in all of this.
Oh.
I guess what the old
folks used to say is right.
You wanna catch a
fellow doing something
he's not supposed to do,
let him catch himself. Hm.
I didn't think it would work.
I figured he'd come in here,
find some way to
set the burglar alarm,
think something was up,
and turn right back around.
Well, desperation.
Desperation and opportunism.
Mr. Fitzmorris here
saw an opportunity
to cash in on what I did to
Senator Crawford in court today.
He saw an opportunity
to frame him real good,
and you weren't about to
let that go by, were you?
Tie clasp.
"L.C."
Lambert Crawford slept here.
He didn't sleep here.
He wasn't having an
affair with Karen. You were.
That's how come you have a key.
That's how come you know
the code to the burglar alarm.
That's absolutely not true.
That's not real proof.
Well, combined
with your fingerprints
in those kitchen gloves...
Kitchen gloves you used
to clean up after the murder.
It casts a long shadow on you.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
We find the defendant,
Melinda Stuart,
not guilty.
Oh, great.
Thank you.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
I would expect the
United States Attorney
to conduct a full investigation
into this conspiracy.
This court is adjourned.
Thanks. You're all wonderful.
Thank you. Thank you.
I've gotta get to the
paper. Thanks, again.
Goodbye. MELINDA: Bye.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And thanks for
leveling with me before.
Maybe I was wrong about you.
No, you weren't.
I just got a phone
call from some people
at the Leyland Group
asking me to help repair
some of the damage
this trial has done to
their corporate image.
Guess what I said?
Good luck.
Mr. Matlock.
Hm. I'm in trouble.
The trial's over, Ben. Not
till he has his last word.
You go ahead.
Yes, sir?
Matlock, you used me.
I don't know what you
mean. Oh, yes, you do.
You knew I'd stop your
examination of Lambert Crawford,
didn't you?
Well, I figured you would.
And you knew the killer
might take this opportunity
to plant new evidence
at the scene of the crime?
Yes, I hoped he would.
And it was all dependent
on me, wasn't it?
Yes.
You used me.
I suppose.
Matlock, I could hate a
man for knowing me that well.
Or you could think
a person like that
was such a fine lawyer,
you'd let him buy you a drink.
You're way out of line.
Hell, it's been a
long day. Hasn't it?
www.tvsubtitles.net